<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sunrise Bay Area</title>
    <link>https://sunrisebayarea.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sunrise Bay Area</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://sunrisebayarea.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Biden Bingo</title>
      <link>https://sunrisebayarea.org/bidenbingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunrisebayarea.org/bidenbingo/</guid>
      <description>Welcome To Office, Now Get To Work!  Joe Biden has been inaugurated as the President of the United States thanks to millions of youth and people of color who turned out in November. Now it&#39;s time that President Biden delivers on this historic mandate to change the direction of this country and confront the multiple intersecting crises we face. We have 100 demands for his first 100 days. Click the link below to get your own Biden Bingo sheet with 25 randomly chosen demands and play along on social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>East Bay Equitable Energy Resilience</title>
      <link>https://sunrisebayarea.org/eastbayenergy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunrisebayarea.org/eastbayenergy/</guid>
      <description>East Bay Equitable Energy Resilience  Overview Energy is a human right, and we must fight for a world in which nobody faces the threat of power shutoff, whether due to wildfire risk, their inability to pay, or where they live. Unfortunately, we do not live in that world yet. One of our hub’s priorities is organizing for a more equitable and resilient energy system here in the East Bay. This work, in partnership with East Bay Clean Power Alliance, is aimed at furthering energy democracy locally in the East Bay, while building the broader movement for utility justice at the state and national level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire/Heatwave Mutual Aid</title>
      <link>https://sunrisebayarea.org/wildfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sunrisebayarea.org/wildfire/</guid>
      <description>Wildfire/Heatwave Mutual Aid  Overview The goal of this campaign is to organize mutual aid and other forms of lasting support for communities most impacted by the fires, smoke, and extreme heat. We can support each other through the fire/heat season and reduce the harmful health impacts with effective mutual aid.
Fill out our interest form     What we do We are providing support and resources to organizations already mobilizing mutual aid in response to fires (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
